In this exercise, you are asked to create an RDS MySQL database with backups enabled,
在此练习中 将要求您创建启用了备份的 RDS MySQL 数据库
and then execute a point in time recovery.
然后执行时间点恢复
Let's walk through and see how it goes.
让我们走过来看看它是如何发生的
We have a database that has been created.
我们拥有已创建的数据库
So if we select our Database,
所以如果我们选择了数据库
go into "Actions" and choose "Restore" to point in time.
进入 "操作 "  然后选择 "复原" 以时间点
When you restore from a snapshot or to a point in time,
从快照复原或复原到时间点时
we always get a new database.
我们总是会有一个新的数据库
So we don't actually change the running database,
所以我们不会改变运行中的数据库
we get a second database.
我们会有第二个数据库
So what this is actually asking us is to give it
所以这其实是要我们给它
information about where to start this new database from.
有关从何处启动此新数据库的信息
So you can see, we can either pick the latest restorable time,
你可以看到 我们可以选择最新的可复原时间
which is basically now,
基本上就是现在
or we can pick a custom time.
或者我们可以选择定制时间
So we pick a custom time,
所以我们选了一个定制时间
we can roll back several days in the past.
我们可以回到过去的几天
So we can pick a point yesterday,
我们可以从昨天开始
we can pick our time, say 6:00 AM,
我们可以选择时间 AM 6:00
and the only other thing that we need to specify is the Database Instance Identifier,
唯一需要指定的是数据库实例标识
which is just the database name.
这只是数据库的名称
That's it. Everything else is the same as it will inherit all the characteristics of
就这样 所有其他的都是一样的 因为它将继承所有
the original database and then we say yes, launch database instance.
原始数据库 然后我们说 " 是 "  启动数据库实例
That will go off and create,
它将会熄灭并产生
and soon we'll have a database restored to yesterday at 6:00 AM.
很快我们就会有一个数据库恢复到昨天 AM 6:00